(Leonard:)Unbelievable.
Mind explaining why you were being
a jerk at the restaurant?
(Leonard:)I was trying to act like we weren't
seeing each other. That was the plan.
(Penny:)The plan was to tell people
we decided to stay friends.
But that's a little hard to do when
you're always being such a toolbag.
(Leonard:)I don't have to stand here
and take this crap.
Where do you think you're going?
(Leonard:)Isn't sex after fighting
kind of what we do now?
(Penny:)Yeah, kind of, yeah.
- What are we doing?
- What do you mean?
(Leonard:)Every scenario I play out
for you and me ends badly.
(Penny:)Because you over-think everything.
(Sheldon's voice:)Leonard, are you listening to me?
- What? Yeah.
- This is a disaster.